[Applause]
i already like this
already i feel like i'm at kid's
birthday party
oh i hit the line she literally hit the
slack
you guys are line good today so today
i will be setting a new world record
which is the most
flips on a slackline in 60 seconds
that line is only two inches wide the
current record for this
is 12 which is going to be very hard to
beat
because for every flip i do i get
dizzier and dizzier
which means it's that much harder for me
to balance on the slack on
because this is the go big show and to
make it harder on myself
i've equipped every single one of you
and bert
with ball guns to try and shoot me off
as i'm going for the record
i'm gonna put on some safety glasses
judges
bert are you guys ready yeah they say
go big or go home i knew it
there you are
open fire
oh my god
oh that's gonna hurt
four five
six seven oh got it
i popped his ass
[Applause]
he's close to the world record oh i
missed him by that much
i keep trying to lead it but it won't
work i want to hit him
11. he's slowing down he's got to be
getting dizzy
[Music]
[Applause]
this is incredible he's still going
19 20 10 seconds ago
23 24
[Applause]
27.
[Music]
you